I'm...
scared of everyone finding out that I'm "Mai".
I'm not confident
I'm a girl that matches your level.
I…
do not know what to do.
But...
I don't want you to hate me.
Like I'd ever hate you.
Having you love me like this, is more than enough.
Aiko... Aiko, let's keep this all a secret,
until you're ready to tell everyone
- that you're "Mai".
- Okay.
Sorry about the wait.
- What are you looking at?
- Huh?
- The weather for tomorrow.
- Oh...
I thought some girl was texting you.
No way.
Hey. What do you think of Aiko Kasumi?
- Oh, that girl that looks like a boy?
- Yeah.
I don't like her. She's a nosy busybody.
I see. I'm glad you guys could make up.
Me too. I'm super happy!
Would you let me ride that happy wave and tell you something?
Thank you, Ai.
I'm officially dating that guy.
Hey! Ritsuki!
[Kasumi]
If you make Hiroko cry, I'll never forgive you!
What are you, her dad?
- What's all this fuss about?
- Did something happen?
- This creep got involved with a high schooler!
- No, no...
It's just platonic between us.
You might call it a chaste relationship of kindred souls—
- Shut up!
- He's totally guilty.
Tip off the cops.
You don't get involved with your little sister's friends!
No matter what you say, it's fine.
Because I'm serious.
I'm serious about Hiroko.
You should worry more about yourself, Sis.
My business has nothing to do with you.
Listen up. Dating wasn't ever the goal.
It was the starting line.
This is the start of the real game.
A game?
He totally dodged the subject.
(T/N: dodge = ronten)
Ronten? Like the jelly?
That would be kanten.
(T/N: kanten = agar jelly)
Now get this...
Can I tell you the greatest test that's awaiting you?
I'm super curious! What is it?
Your part-time job!
Crap! Text me when he tells you.
I'm not interested!
Ritsuki, don't fill her head with weird ideas.
- Your hamburger.
- What?
What came over me?!
I'm just thinking about our sister's future here.
What's... the test?
The great test will be...
you.
Me?
Hiroko told me. You're keeping Mai a secret, huh?
So what?
Your boyfriend is a popular guy.
Can you watch in silence while girls fawn over him in front of you?
I'll be fine!
That secret is a pretty substantial test.
I told you, I'll be fine!
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 4]
All right, time for a match!
Yeah, fine by me.
Okay, stop!
- You can't.
- Why not?!
- Boys and girls are having separate training sessions today.
- Huh?!
Come on, come on. Let's go, Reo!
Okay! This way, Kasumi.
What?!
32... 33...
- 34... 35...
- Don't slow down, girls! Be like Kasumi!
36...
Ai? Are you all right?
I'm fine!
I'm fine! Stupid test...
Excuse me, ladies.
Great work today, Reo!
It's fine!
- That's all right...
- Why not? It's fine!
You sure have a big appetite, Reo.
I'll make food for you next time.
- No thank you.
- Why not?
She's unbelievable...
- Does his girlfriend know?
- If she did, wouldn't she fight over him?
Let's go tell his maid girlfriend about it.
Good idea!
Ai?
Oh, Erena. Want my rice ball?
Are you sure?
Thank you!
It's almost like I can hear you deflating.
Reo will always be surrounded by girls like that, huh?
When you fall in love, some things become painful.
That's true. Things are different from they were before.
But there's also
a happiness you've never felt before, right?
I wonder...
But in your case,
it must hurt not being able to tell everyone you're Reo's girlfriend.
Maybe I'm not fine, after all.
Will you stop keeping the secret?
I'll always support you.
And your secret.
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
Thank you.
♫ It seems it won't end in a draw ♫
♫ You hated loosing, ♫
♫ So I won't let you go easy on me ♫
Reo!
Let's walk home together!
- Reo!
- I want to walk home with you!
- Let's come with you!
♫ I want to steal you away
The secret that belongs to only us. 1on1 ♫
You look like you're going to cry.
♫ I make you acting like a kid with just a sweet kiss ♫
You smiled so much before.
Is there something bothering you?
No, there's not.
How long have you been there, anyway?
You're a funny girl.
When I think you're going to smile, you almost start crying.
And now you're angry.
Buzz off. Don't talk to me.
♫ Lips to exchange ♫
It's hopeless!
I have to be my usual Aiko-self so they don't find out my secret!
[I'm going to Spica tomorrow.]
[Let's make time to hang out by ourselves.]
[That'd make me so happy!]
Great work today!
I'll make food for you next time.
Let's walk home together!
[DON'T come.]
[Why not?]
[Because! See you tomorrow. Night.]
Oh! Looking for Mai?
Would I be here for any other reason?
There's a girl that looks a lot like Mai, right?
Might be funny to tease her about it.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
I just find you two very entertaining.
Thank you.
Why did you come?
Forget that. You need to be careful.
You're the one who needs to be careful.
Takumi might've realized who you are.
There's no way.
Are you angry?
I mean, I told you not to come.
Ikumi's trying to go after you.
- I told you, Morikawa—
- Reo!
Did you call for me?
No, he didn't.
I wasn't asking you, Mai!
I see...
Oh? I guess Mai surrendered you to me!
- I don't think so.
- Huh?
It's weird to see you not fight.
- Whoopsie!
- Oh my god, I'm so sorry!
Ikumi gets misunderstood by girls, so I have to protect her.
I think she's been through a lot.
So I can't be too hard on her.
I love that about you, Ai.
What are you doing? Come on...
Reo wants another coffee.
- I'll take care of it.
- No, I will.
- I will!
Relax, you guys!
Tough luck! More customers have arrived.
She's so softhearted.
Welcome ho— no way!
- How adorable!
- This place is so cute!
What's the matter?!
- Oh, Reo!
- We came, too!
- I've never been to a maid cafe!
- The coffee is really good here.
- Sounds great!
You'll have to introduce us to Mai!
- Introduce?
- Where is Mai?
Oh! There she is!
Why are you here, Morikawa?!
You're bothering the other guests, so could you please keep it down?
What? You're such a pain. The maid look is ugly on you.
Why are you always where Reo is?
This is bad. Ikumi is alone with those girls.
You stay here for now. I'll figure something out.
Take care of Ai.
Take care of...?
It's rude to Mai!
- But I'm worried!
- Just hide! It'd be bad if they found out, right?
Yeah, but...
I'll go out there too, okay?
- You're with Reo way too much!
- Yeah, way too much!
And that maid outfit looks like crap on you!
Just calm down, you guys. You too, Morikawa.
They're so scary! Please help me, Reo!
Let go of him!
Quiet.
I have an idea.
What's going on? An argument?
Ritsuki, could you take off your clothes?
What are you talking about?
- Why are you helping her?
- Listen...
- She's just taking advantage of you!
- Where is Mai, anyway?
- That's enough. We're in a cafe.
- But...
And anyway, who I date is none of your business.
Well, Morikawa needs to get her paws off!
- Right!
- Get off now!
Miss, I'm afraid we can't have a racket in the store.
Let go of me. What is this?
Please don't use your beautiful hands for something like this.
He's a butler?
I'm terribly sorry for my maid's rudeness.
I will attend to your any wish today, my lady.
I'm sorry.
- He's amazing!
- Super handsome!
He pulled it off.
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
I think the first-aid kit is around here.
Could you hurry it up? We'll be here until morning.
Sorry. I'll go ask about it.
Hey, do you know where the first-aid kit is?
Ritsuki put it away last time, but...
Ugh! Where is he?
Tidying up outside with Reo.
Getting full use out of him, huh?
Thanks for today.
I know you were probably just helping Ikumi, but...
No. I did it for you.
I wanted to protect you, Mai.
How slick! You must be popular with girls.
But I know you really did it to protect Ikumi.
That's true.
You two must be really close.
I'm sure Ikumi is happy to have you protecting her.
I would do anything for her.
Here it is. The thing you were looking for.
Thanks.
Sorry for having you help me clean up.
I can't do a thing about people issues, though.
Sorry.
It is a mystery. You don't have trouble with the ladies. Why Aiko?
There's other fish in the sea, right?
To me, Aiko is the best.
Ikumi's pretty cute, huh?
I think she's way better than Aiko—
I'm not interested in anyone else.
Well, if that's true...
then don't make her worry.
Okay.
What are you talking about?
Boobies.
- Apparently, Reo likes them big!
- What?
Are you trying to pick a fight?
I'm sorry about today.
I couldn't protect you.
It's fine.
I want to sit down and have a talk with Morikawa.
- To tell her Mai is really Aiko?
- No, not that.
What she wants will never come true.
I'll go tell her that.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
Took your sweet time!
Reo.
You seem well.
Mai is really nice, huh? Surrendering you to me again.
I would never give you up to anyone.
She must not like you all that much, huh?
Mai is
in love with me.
Whoa... You're awfully confident, aren't you?
If she didn't love me, I would be in big trouble.
Why is that?
Because
I really, really love Mai.
So, Morikawa—
Please,
don't say any more.
I mean,
I haven't done anything yet.
Stop holding out hope for me.
What's wrong?
I want him.
I want Reo!
So?
What should I do?
An amusement park?! Let's go, let's go!
You don't have work next Saturday, right?
- I don't have basketball, either.
- That's great!
I can't wait!
- What do you want to ride?
- Well, I want a hot dog...
And a crepe...
- Those are foods.
- Huh?
- What rides?
- Rides?
Rides? Let's go on a roller coaster!
- Yeah. Let's do it.
- Yeah!
Seduce Mai.
I understand.
[Next time]
Dates are super fun, aren't they?
Found you!
Ikumi is trying to steal your boyfriend.
I'm fine with half of what Mai has, so please love me.
Morikawa could probably become an ideal girlfriend.
If you're serious, Ikumi, I'll accept your challenge.
[This drama is a work of fiction]